以下是这部分的纲要
Here is the outline for this section.
In machine learning, we have a problem to solve.
在机器学习中 我们面临着需要解决的问题
Normally, the problem corresponds to evaluating some data and making predictions.
通常 该问题对应的是评估一些数据并作出预测
问题用这个损坏的汽车表示
The problem is represented by this broken car over here.
Now, in order to solve it,
要解决该问题
我们有几个工具
we have a few tools.
These tools are the algorithms,
这些工具就是算法
例如线性回归 逻辑回归 SVM
things like linear or logistic regression, SVM's,
神经网络 决策树 等等
neural networks, decision trees, etc.
如何知道哪个工具效果最好呢？
How do we know which tool works best?
Well, for that we have a bunch of measurement tools
我们可以使用各种衡量工具
来评估所有的算法
and we use them to evaluate all the algorithms.
Once we evaluate the algorithms and
评估算法和算法参数
their parameters and decide which ones are best for a problem,
并判断哪些工具最适合解决我们的问题
then, we go ahead and solve our problem.
然后去解决我们的问题
在这节课
In this section, we learn
我们将学习衡量工具 即学习各种指标和技巧
the measurement tools so we'll learn a bunch of metrics and techniques that will
来判断算法何时可以有效处理数据
tell us when an algorithm is working well with
如何调整算法以便获得最佳效果
the data and how to tweak them to work best for us.